

## CONTACT

info.devalan@gmail.com

322 200 95 81

Website

Github

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

#### SKILLS

•••• Project management

•••• Software development

• • • • Cost analysis and budgets

•••• Resource planning

••• Staff and user training

## PROGRAMS

PHP LARAVEL

HTML CSS

WORDPRESS JQUERY

API REST GI

JAVASCRIPT SQL

REACT

## LANGUAGES

•••• Español

•••• English

# ALÁN CÓRDOVA

## FRONTEND / BACKEND DEVELOPER

#### PROFILE

Self motivated web developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hard-working with an inclination to meet deadlines. Interested in the role of the company that promotes best practices and offers various client projects, with 10 years of experience in developing Frontend and Backend .

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Carbono Marketing, Puerto Vallarta

Full Stack Web Developer | MARCH 2021 - MARCH 2023

- Development of multiple sites for different types of clients from simple pages to reservation systems.
- Optimized corporate website based on Wordpress technology.
- Integration of eCommerce on the corporate site to increase customer engagement.
- Creation of a sales management system,
  employment exchange and incidents developed in Laravel
- Creation of development guidelines for the IT team.
- Management of WHM and Cpanel accounts.
- Personnel management and leadership of the development team

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## SB Realtors, Puerto Vallarta

Full Stack Web Developer | MARCH 2016 - JULY 2020

- Websites tested and troubleshooting before deployment.
- Optimized and repaired corporate website based on Wordpress technology.
- Revised code to validate structures, evaluate security and verify browser, device and operating system compatibility.
- Developed the SBRealtors eCommerce website, resulting in increased online sales after the launch date.
- Performing unit tests to offer optimal browser functionality. I have collected, defined and translated user requirements into project designs and implementation plans.
- Requirements analyzed and software applications designed, developed and implemented for multiple websites.
- Programming capabilities used in PHP, SQL, and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Took concepts and produced design mock-ups and prototypes to strengthen designs, improve user experiences and site interactions.
- Developed online pages and applications using Laravel.
- Design of the site created and user interface using HTML and CSS practices.
- User support was provided to customers to train, educate, and answer questions.
- Collaboration with in-house web designers to create elegant designs.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Vallarta Lifestyles, Puerto Vallarta

Full Stack Web Developer | MARCH 2016 - JULY 2020

- Efficient large-scale software implementations, including test functions and correction code.
- Revised code, debugged issues, and fixed issues.
- Coordination with other programmers to evaluate and improve software and hardware interfaces.
- Ideas and suggestions were contributed in team meetings and updates on deadlines, designs and improvements were provided.
- Maintenance of existing applications and design and delivery of new applications.
- Worked closely with clients to establish specifications.

## EDUCATION

## GED, Centro Universitario de la Costa, Puerto Vallarta

AUGUST 2006 - JULY 2010

Certificate, C.B.T.I.S., Puerto Vallarta

AUGUST 2003 - JULY 2006

Certificate, Escuela Secundaria Técnica #81, Puerto AUGUST 2003 – JULY 2003

## REFERENCES

Alexis Silva Brisset | CEO - SB GROUP PVR alexis@sbpvr.com | +52 322 221 00 51

**Hugo de la Torre | CEO - Carbono Marketing** hugo@carbonomarketing.com | +52 322 125 73 10

Victor Arreola | Brand Manager -Carbono Marketing

victor@carbonomarketing.com | +52 322 355 14 91